mollywoodtimes.com 2018-06-25

# Privacy Policy - Mollywood Times

We at Mollywood times protects information you share with us by all means of trust and faith.

**Our privacy policy benefits  **

This policy describes you, details about how we collects information from you and how we use it all  
your personal information when you use any of our websites related to Mollywood times .

**Data from other social networking websites and related sources**

You can stay in touch with us through various contents such as pictures , videos ,write up , notes ,  
and blog posts through various third party applications such as Facebook, Google plus , twitter and  
links available through third party sites or our affiliated services.

When you use your account or else our content on or through third party social networking sites or  
by any other means , you may give opportunity to us for reaching certain information from your  
social media profile from your interaction with us like your name ,email address, birthday, age,  
photos, location, tags, quotes, friend lists , following lists ,posts, and likes you make .

By sharing information from your profiles you can help us in providing exclusive contents , helping to  
stay in touch with you directly or via social networking sites with the latest buzz and trends in this  
fast growing technical media world .

We also inform you that your information on internet is viable to various other websites based on  
your privacy settings, there for we cannot stop further use of your information because it could be  
seen by anyone using the internet .

**Contents Related to Movies**  
songs , videos, and Images related to movies we uses on the website is under the sole  
proprietorship of the producer and his production company. Any enquiries related to movie and news  
can be forwarded to us directly via our email id – [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

**About Movie reviews  **

Movie reviews are based on our personal perceptions. Once it is published no further changes are  
possible and we don’t take orders from anyone like stars, fans , directors , producers, and any  
representatives to change our decision

To whom we share your personal data  
1) Credit reporting and fraud checking agencies.  
2) Our related companies and members of mollywood times.  
3) Government and other related authorities.  
4) Content partners and advertisers  
5) Tele Communication and information service providers. .

Contact us for any further assistance or enquiries about your use of personal information, please

write to us at
